The Real Life Video Game
So these stars, spears, swords come flying at you from nowhere.
You're this ninja and have to dodge them.
You get #10 points, if you make it to the end of the round.
#10 points, here I come!
However, if an enemy Samurai appears, you have to but go back.
If you don't dodge it in time, you die.
You have only three lives.
Then game over.
That means failing thrice is game over!
Exactly!
Give it a go, Shizuka-chan!
Why, thank you!
Hey, move right, fast!!!
I prefer simple games like this, for once!
I worked hard to get my hands on it.
It's a tough game...
But I've already got to #50 points!
Darn! I only got to #190 points!
What?!
-#190 points?!
Magnets are something, indeed!
Now my turn!
You'll get a dozens of Zeroes at first, but have heart, my friend...
Why, sure...
I guess it's very hard for first-timers...
Yay, I got #310 points!
What?! You must be kidding me...!
How cool!
You're so good, Suneo-san!
I'm really good at games like these...
Nobita-san, please give us a second chance!? Pretty pleaseee~...?!
This time, I'll be sure to get 500 points!
Gotta practice, so soooorrrrry!
See ya~!
Ah, Nobita-san!
Yo, Nobita.
What a nice thing you have got there in your hands.
Care to give it to me?!
What's with that face of yours?!
Umm... welll... It's nothing really....
Just gimme!
It's too easy for you, Giant...
You'll get bored of it in no time...
Oh, shaddup!
Oh, no, I only made it to #170 points!
What a genius!
Hmph! This is too easy for me!
I made it to #310 points!
What?!
Even Shizuka-chan made it to #190 points!
But for me, it was just luck...!
Nobita, gimme one more chance!
I'll be #1 in no time!
Dammit, this time I'll...!!!
Giant, please gimme back my game...!
I'll be borrowing this till I best all o' you...!
You can't be serious...!
Once in a while, I do gymnastics!
'Yo, it feels so refreshin'!!!
Oh!
Welcome home, Nobita-kun!
What happened? You look down...
Don't tell me that Giant took away your NInja game...?!
"Lemme have it for a while", he said..
But Giant never returns anything he takes from you!
It cost me three years of my savings, but now it's gone!
My life is over!
The Real Life Video Game!
I can't see you crying like this, so...
Thanks, Doraemon.
But what's this supposed to be? It's a see-through screen!
It uses real people.
Real people?
FIrst, you try it out, Nobita-kun!
Me?
Anyone will do.
First set the target.
Next set the moving screen....
Here!
Then, set the background!
Last, hit the preset button and we're good to go!
W-What's going on here?!
The falling objects will be different,...
But otherwise it uses the same principles as the good ol' Ninja game.
Game start!
Let's play it outside!
It uses the holographic objects that vanish upon falling.
Oops!
It only hurts so little when hit!
But that hurts!
Did you like it?
Not bad!
It's no fun game for the target person.
You think he's still there?
Found him!
Just you wait, play my game all you want, but now...
First, set the target!
Then set the background...
And now, it's playtime!
Then hit the preset button and we're good to go!
What 'da hell???!!!
Game start!
What?!
Things are getting interesting!
#10 points won!
All right! Next up #20 points!
What 'da hell is goin' on 'ere?!
You can restart the game!
Sum 'un, please help me!
Ha, so it's them!
Left... Oops, right...!
Suneo saw us!
This is no good!
Let's talk to him.
Doraemon!
Shh, come here!
Let me try it too!
What?!
I'm gonna bully Giant!
Uh, sure...
Here you go, Suneo!
The principles are the same as the good ol' Ninja game.
That's great!
Move!
Again?!
Wut 'da hell?
He's hit!
Only two more rounds!
I know!
Things are getting tough and interesting!
He had got #310 points earlier.
What?!
He ain't worth even #10 points!
You're deliberately getting him hit!
So you found me out, huh?
I'm payin' him back for the morning!
Oh, brother!
You can't!
It's my turn now!
One more try, please!
No!
-I see you up there!!!
He saw us!
Get down at once!
This is payback!
Take that!
Oh, no, it hit Mr. Kaminari's window!
Why you, little punk...!!!
Oh, this is just like a real Ninja game!
He's gonna uproot Suneo's score!
Wish this would last forever!
You got that right!
Damn you, kid!
Sorry!
I had enough of this!